▍2026 美网 男单半决赛
谢尔顿 4-6 6-3 6-3 7-5 蒂亚福 · 赛后场上采访
Well, Ben, you've just made
谢尔顿 你刚刚打进了
your very first Grand Slam final
生涯第一个大满贯决赛
and you've done it on home soil.
而且是在自己的主场
Talk to me about the significance
跟我聊聊这场球
of this match,
意味着什么
especially considering you played
尤其是这一场
such a good friend in Frances for your spot
你要跟蒂亚福这样的好朋友
in the final.
争一个决赛席位
Yeah, I mean, first on FO,
嗯 首先说蒂亚福
he's like a he's like a big brother to me.
他对我来说就像大哥一样
To to be honest, every time that we get
说实话 每一次
to take this court together, Arthur Ashe
我们能一起站上阿瑟·阿什
and play each other is super special.
在这儿交手 都意义非凡
But this is where we want
但我们想站的就是这个位置
to be at the at the tail end
在一项赛事
of this tournament.
打到最后的时候
This is both of our favorite tournament
这是我们俩最爱的赛事
in the world, our favorite court in the world.
也是我们最爱的球场
And to be able to light it up in front
能在你们面前
of you guys is the best feeling
把这儿点燃
that there is.
是世上最好的感觉
You made the semis here three years ago.
三年前你在这儿打进半决赛
You made the semis here again.
今年你又一次打进半决赛
What's different about the Ben Shelton here
2026 年的谢尔顿
in 2026 as opposed to the Ben Shelton
和第一次闯进美网半决赛的他
that made his very first US Open semi?
有什么不一样？
Yeah, I think I've grown up.
嗯 我觉得我长大了
I'm more mature, more focused.
更成熟 也更专注
I know what my goal is.
我知道我的目标是什么
I know what my job is out here
知道我在这儿的任务是什么
and I'm 100% committed to those goals.
百分之百扑在那些目标上
It's not easy playing here
在这儿打球本来就不容易
on Arthur Ashe.
这里是阿瑟·阿什球场
You're playing in front
你打球的时候 台下坐着
of all your favorite athletes
全是你最喜欢的运动员
and and movie movie stars.
还有电影明星
So to be able to keep your head down
所以能一直低着头
and focus for over 3 hours
专注三个多小时
is not an easy task.
真的不是件容易的事
I keep on looking up at the
我总是忍不住抬头
at the screen like, "Oh, shoot.
看那块大屏幕 心想 哎呀
Jaylen Brunson's here." So, I got to ask this.
布伦森也来了 那我得问这个
2003 since the last time
上一次美国男子拿下这个冠军
an American man won this title,
还是 2003 年
but it's been since 1972 that a black man
而上一次有黑人球员
has played in the final of the US Open
打进美网决赛
and it was Arthur Ashe.
要追溯到 1972 年的阿瑟·阿什
On Sunday, you will step foot
周日你将踏上
on the on Arthur Ashe Stadium looking
阿瑟·阿什球场
to take your very first Grand Slam title.
去争夺生涯第一个大满贯冠军
When you hear
当你听到这些
that, what goes through your mind
在为周日做准备的时候
as you prepare for Sunday?
心里会想些什么？
Yeah, it's a lot of emotion.
嗯 百感交集
My dad my mom has s sacrificed a lot
我爸爸 我妈妈为我付出了太多
for me to be in this position today.
才有我今天站在这里
My my dad lost his mom earlier
我爸爸今年早些时候
this year and and she's the reason
失去了他的母亲 而正是因为她
that he was able to play tennis.
他才有机会打网球
Without her, you know,
没有她
there's no Ben Shelton standing here today.
就没有今天站在这儿的谢尔顿
So, th this one is for her.
所以 这一个是为她赢的
This one is for her.
这一个 是为她
And I'm going to need you guys
周日我需要你们
on Sunday to to bring the energy.
把气氛给我点起来
I'm going for it here.
我会全力去拼
I'm going to leave it all on the court.
把所有东西都留在球场上
I hope you guys come and back me.
希望你们能来支持我
Let's do this for the USA.
为美国 我们一起拿下
And one more thing.
还有一件事
And one more thing, it's a it's
今天这个日子
a difficult day to be out here playing.
站在这儿打球其实很不容易
My thoughts and prayers go out to all
我的心和祈祷 献给所有
the families who are impacted by 9/11.
被 9/11 影响的家庭
This is one
这里是
of the greatest greatest cities in the world
世界上最伟大的城市之一
and one of the biggest tragedies,
也承受过最大的悲剧之一
but, yeah, thoughts and prayers
愿我们的思念和祈祷
to everyone involved and affected.
陪着每一个经历过的人
Thank you guys.
谢谢你们
Rest assured, New York's going to come out
放心 周日整个纽约
for you on Sunday, ladies and gentlemen,
都会为你而来 女士们先生们
through to his first US Open final.
他闯进了生涯第一个美网决赛